scrubtheweb.com 2010-06-23

# Scrub The Web Privacy Policy

In general, Scrub The Web does not collect, store, use or disclose personally identifying information except in very specific instances, such as, for example, when you enroll as a Member or advertiser/merchant, as defined below. The instances in which Scrub The Web does collect and use information are specifically described in this Privacy Policy.

Scrub The Web provides fun, easy to use services, including Scrub The Web Search (located at www.scrubtheweb.com) and Scrub The Web Website SEO services (located at www.scrubtheweb/abs/) (the "Services"). The Services are made available by Scrub The Web and, its subsidiaries and affiliates. Scrub The Web values its users and their concerns about privacy. To this end, Scrub The Web engages in consistent information practices and uses its best efforts to make clear disclosures regarding those practices. This Privacy Policy is a part of that effort.

Your 234x60 image, HTML or text message could be placed here. Check our rates.

### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Scrub The Web. If there are any exceptions, we will clearly disclose them prior to collecting any information, and will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide the information.

Please be aware that, as part of the Services, Scrub The Web provides links to Websites operated by third parties, and also provides search results and similar services to third parties for display on their own Websites or applications. Scrub The Web is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Websites or applications. Also, please be aware that advertisements on Scrub The Web may be provided by a third party, which may collect cookies as part of the process of serving those ads. These cookies are typically used for the purpose of tracking performance of the advertisements. Scrub The Web does not determine which information will be collected by that third party. Please see the paragraph below regarding Third Party Advertisements.

### Third Party Advertisements.

Scrub The Web may use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

### What information does Scrub The Web collect and how is it used?

Does Scrub The Web disclose information to third parties? Scrub The Web may collect any or all of the following three types of information: (a) traffic or clickstream data, (b) cookies, or (c) contact information and other personally identifying information. Scrub The Web's collection and use of each type of data is described below, as well as the ways (if any) in which the data may be shared with third parties.

**(a) Traffic or Clickstream Data.** Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. Scrub The Web may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of people visited a certain area on our Website or searched Websites for the term "apple pies". Scrub The Web collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) users access. For example, Scrub The Web's servers collect information about the site from which you entered to enable Scrub The Web to calculate and pay its affiliates if any, information about the most frequently searched terms to help its advertisers provide the most relevant search results, information about usage to check for fraudulent behavior or other abnormalities and to ensure that our Services are technically superior. In addition to the forgoing applications, Scrub The Web uses the information (in aggregate form) to better design the Services.

**(b) Cookies. Like many sites, Scrub The Web may collect information about online behavior using cookies.** These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning, as well as to streamline their experiences using the Services. Cookies lets us know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services. Scrub The Web may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our affiliates and other business partners. To Scrub The Web, using information within cookies is a way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our Services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services. Scrub The Web may share information about usage of the Services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**(c) Contact Information or Personally Identifying Information.** Scrub The Web can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become a Member, advertiser or merchant with Scrub The Web, provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from Scrub The Web and provide your name or return contact information, (2) when you register for the advanced features of Scrub The Web, or (3) in connection with special offers or contests.

Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. This information is not stored or used in connection with traffic or clickstream data and is provided to a third party only as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request.

Scrub The Web may use registration information to make users aware of new products or special offers or promotions. Scrub The Web will abide by requests from you (in accordance with the procedure below) to discontinue such use. Scrub The Web stores personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely (as described below) and considers it part of the assets of its business. With your permission, Scrub The Web will not provide registration information to third parties.

Finally, you may choose to provide contact information, other personally identifying information, and demographic information in order to participate in optional surveys or contests, which are run for promotional purposes. Scrub The Web uses such information to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win the contest. Finally, from time to time, but only with your permission, Scrub The Web may provide certain of its users' registration information to selected third parties who wish to participate in special promotions offered in conjunction with Scrub The Web. Users may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time by contacting Scrub The Web.

Your 234x60 image, HTML or text message could be placed here. Check our rates.

### Is data stored by Scrub The Web secure?

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Scrub The Web has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Scrub The Web (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Scrub The Web will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

### Does Scrub The Web collect personally identifying information from or about children?

Scrub The Web uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The Services are not targeted at children, and children may not register for any portions of the Services that require registration.

### How can I access or correct any personally identifying information about me?

To request a copy of the personally identifiable information you have sent to Scrub The Web, please contact us by clicking on the " **Contact Us** " link found on virtually all pages throughout our site. You must provide your full name and the email from which the request is received (and to which the response will be sent) must match the email on file with Scrub The Web. You may then correct or delete such information using the procedures specified in the email.

### How do I find out more about Scrub The Web's information practices?

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact Scrub The Web as follows:

Business and Legal Affairs  
Scrub The Web  
1080 E. Pecos Rd Ste 18-425  
Chandler, AZ 85225-0600  
Tel: 480.633.5548  
Fax: 480.626.8410

You may also use the above contact information if you think any information about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or if you want to change the sort of information about you that Scrub The Web may have collected.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on June 11, 2009.
